<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Proverbs</string>
    <string name="MA1">\"Waste no more time arguing what a good man should be. Be One.\"</string>
    <string name="MA2">\"It never ceases to amaze me: we all love ourselves more than other people, but care more about their opinion than our own\".</string>
    <string name="Epictectus1">\"It’s not because things are difficult that we dare not venture. It’s because we dare not venture that they are difficult.\"</string>
    <string name="MA3">\"You have power over your mind — not outside events. Realize this, and you will find strength.\"</string>
    <string name="Seneca1">\“Difficulties strengthen the mind, as labor does the body.\” </string>
    <string name="Rumi1">\“If you are irritated by every rub, how will your mirror be polished?\”</string>
    <string name="Socrates1">\“Having the fewest wants, I am nearest to the gods.\”</string>
    <string name="Epictectus2">\“What upsets people is not things themselves, but their judgements about these things.\”</string>
    <string name="Epictectus3">\“How long are you going to wait before you demand the best for yourself.\”</string>
    <string name="Epictectus4">\“First say to yourself what you would be; and then do what you have to do.\” </string>
    <string name="Epictectus5">\“Anything or anyone capable of angering you becomes your master.”\</string>
    <string name="proverbs_12">\"It is better to live in a desert than with a quarrelsome and nagging wife.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_13">\"A hot-tempered person stirs up conflict, but the one who is patient calms a quarrel.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_14">\"Do you see a person wise in their own eyes? There is more hope for a fool than for them.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_15">\"The rich are wise in their own eyes; one who is poor and discerning sees how deluded they are.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_16">\"Wounds from a friend can be trusted, but an enemy multiplies kisses.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_17">\"A fool’s lips walk into a fight, and his mouth invites a beating.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_18">\"Whoever loves discipline loves knowledge, but whoever hates correction is stupid.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_19">\"Whoever disregards discipline comes to poverty and shame, but whoever heeds correction is honored.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_20">\"Do not wear yourself out to get rich; do not trust your own cleverness.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_21">\"Do you see someone skilled in their work? They will serve before kings; they will not serve before obscure men.\"</string>
    <string name="proverbs_22">\"To acquire wisdom is to love oneself; people who cherish understanding will prosper.\" (Proverbs 19:8)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_23">\"A fool shows his annoyance at once, but a prudent person overlooks an insult.\" (Proverbs 12:16)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_24">\"The rich rule over the poor, and the borrower is slave to the lender.\" (Proverbs 22:7)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_25">\"Sluggards do not plow in season; so at harvest time they look but find nothing.\" (Proverbs 20:4)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_26">\"A false witness will not go unpunished, and whoever pours out lies will not go free.\" (Proverbs 19:5)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_27">\"Whoever trusts in his own mind is a fool, but he who walks in wisdom will be delivered.\" (Proverbs 28:26)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_28">\"Do not say, ‘I’ll pay you back for this wrong!’ Wait for the Lord, and He will avenge you.\" (Proverbs 20:22)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_29">\"When pride comes, then comes disgrace, but with humility comes wisdom.\" (Proverbs 11:2)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_30">\"A generous person will prosper; whoever refreshes others will be refreshed.\" (Proverbs 11:25)</string>
    <string name="proverbs_01">Proverbs 21:19</string>
    <string name="proverbs_02">Proverbs 15:18</string>
    <string name="proverbs_03">Proverbs 26:12</string>
    <string name="proverbs_04">Proverbs 28:11</string>
    <string name="proverbs_05">Proverbs 27:6</string>
    <string name="proverbs_06">Proverbs 18:6</string>
    <string name="proverbs_07">Proverbs 24:5</string>
    <string name="proverbs_08">Proverbs 13:18</string>
    <string name="proverbs_09">Proverbs 23:4</string>
    <string name="proverbs_010">Proverbs 22:29</string>
    <string name="proverbs_011">Proverbs 19:8</string>
    <string name="proverbs_012">Proverbs 12:16</string>
    <string name="proverbs_013">Proverbs 22:7</string>
    <string name="proverbs_014">Proverbs 20:4</string>
    <string name="proverbs_015">Proverbs 19:5</string>
    <string name="proverbs_016">Proverbs 28:26</string>
    <string name="proverbs_017">Proverbs 20:22</string>
    <string name="proverbs_018">Proverbs 11:2</string>
    <string name="proverbs_019">Proverbs 11:25</string>
    <string name="MA">Marcus Aurelius</string>
    <string name="EP">Epictectus</string>
    <string name="Socrates">Socrates</string>
    <string name="Seneca">Seneca</string>
    <string name="Rumi">Rumi</string>
</resources>